Linus Peng

1012/601 Little Lonsdale Street • Melbourne • VIC 3000

Phone (61) 0416-468482 • E-MAIL penxumelb@gmail.com • Website: https://linusmelb.github.io

EDUCATION The University of Melbourne

Bachelor of Science, Computing and Software Systems

National University of Singapore - 2017.07 - 2017.12

Exchange program, Computer Science (Melbourne Global Scholars Award)

SUMMARY

Innovative tech mind with 3 years of experience working as a software developer. Capable of working with a variety of technology and software solutions, and managing databases. A valuable team member who has experience diagnosing problems and developing solutions. Talented programmer with unique ideas and a huge passion for learning new things.

SKILLS Analytics Service: GA, GTM, Firebase analytics (App tracking)

Database: BigQuery, MSSQL, Mysql, MongoDB **Cloud Platform:** GCP, Azure, Digitalocean

Deployment Tools: Jenkins

Proxy Server: Nginx

RCS: Git

Others: Kubernetes, Webpack, Tableau, Data Studio, Vuejs

EXPERIENCE

Webjet Limited (ASX: WEB), Analytics Developer

2018.11 - Present

- Wrote and optimized query code under BigQuery to handle large data sets using partitioning; the data loads are approximately 10GB/day
- Implemented full GA tracking on Covermore & Bali Buddy whitelabel pages (Including pageview, click, enhanced ecommerce funnel)
- Worked with Facebook & Criteo's Engineering Team to implement third party pixels for dynamic remarketing
- Implemented firebase tracking on Webjet's iOS and Android apps
- Built an analytics website (Vue.js, Flask, and Kubernetes) to manage all jobs in the ETL system

Novatti Group Limited(ASX: NOV), Software developer & SEO developer 2018.07 – 2018.10

- Project link https://www.chinapayments.com
- Led, architected and participated in the design, testing, and deployment of client/server
- Designed a brand new UI for the site and Integrated Bootstrap4 and ParticleJs into the site
- Handled problems/issues and make prompt solutions to resolve them
- Helped boost the company's online presence & website traffic

Radio Fodder - University of Melbourne Student Radio, Web developer 2018.01 – 2018.08

- Project link http://www.radiofodder.com
- Redesigned and developed the site individually
- Integrated a new online radio system into the site

Chinese Students and Scholars Association (CSSA), Head of IT department 2016.09 – 2017.09

- Project link http://www.cssaunimelb.com
- Designed a brand new website for CSSA
- Developed a membership management system to store more than 5000+ members' information
- Manage and support critical online information systems of CSSA

MelMel Consulting PTY LTD, Software Developer 2015.06 – 2017.01

- Project link:
 - o http://www.reioiceworld.com.au
 - o http://www.melmel.com.au/service
 - Revised programming and software development projects by updating code and working to improve functionality.
 - Designed and deployed the WordPress website for customers

OTHER PROJECTS	Second-hand marketplace(10k+ users): https://xdd.com.au Subject rating platform(6.8k users): https://uzhan.com.au AddressBook (Java): https://github.com/LinusMelb/main
LANGUAGE	English – Fluent Mandarin – Native